{
    "subject": "Jon_Hall",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Frances_Langford",
    "human_readable": "Jon Hall is married to Frances Langford.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9885579347610474,
            "question": "Is Frances Langford married to Jon Hall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9145376682281494,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Jon Hall and Frances Langford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.897404134273529,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Jon Hall and Frances Langford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8786535263061523,
            "question": "Who is Jon Hall married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6603559255599976,
            "question": "What is the name of Jon Hall's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6541003584861755,
            "question": "What is the name of Jon Hall's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6484624743461609,
            "question": "Who is Frances Langford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3688136041164398,
            "question": "Does Jon Hall have any other family members?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36257249116897583,
            "question": "Who are some notable people in Frances Langford's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3601302206516266,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Jon Hall's family?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jon Hall is married to Frances Langford.",
            "html": "yago_6921_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some notable people in Frances Langford's life?",
            "html": "yago_6921_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Jon Hall have any other family members?",
            "html": "yago_6921_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Frances Langford?",
            "html": "yago_6921_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6921_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6921_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6921_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6921_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6921_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6921_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6921_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6921_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6921_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6921_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Jon Hall is married to Frances Langford\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe context information contains several documents that mention Jon Hall and Frances Langford as a couple. Document #2 explicitly states that they were married for 20 years, and document #39 mentions them as first husband and wife, respectively. These statements support the triple that Jon Hall is married to Frances Langford."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Jon Hall is married to Frances Langford.\" The details about their marriage, including the dates of when they dated, got together, were married, and divorced are provided in multiple files."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}